<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New Haven &amp; Fairfield County's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Jonathan Carbutti, a top Real Estate Agent in New Haven &amp; Fairfield County, shares his own internal real estate agent training for free. His Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 15:14:44 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 15:14:44 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Where Can I Find the Best Road Map to Success?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vDC027EiWnk?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here’s how we can help you get started on the right foot in 2021.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re at the end of 2020, which means that it’s time for 2021 individual business planning. If you don’t have a written business plan for next year, you don’t have a GPS or roadmap for your success. We’ve had agents go from $2.2 million to over $6.2 million, and the only difference they made was writing out a business plan. &lt;strong&gt;I cannot stress to you enough the importance of a simple, written business plan.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want a copy of the simple business plan we use, feel free to reach out via phone or email. We’d also be happy to answer any real estate-related questions you might have.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 13:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/where-can-i-find-the-best-road-map-to-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/where-can-i-find-the-best-road-map-to-success.html</guid>
        
        <category>Real Estate Agents</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: Is Your Business Flourishing?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FubaKWVjshQ?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;No matter if you’re new or established, we want to help your business grow.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a brand-new agent or have been considering a career in real estate, today I’m speaking directly to you. Our team has been growing—we just recently hired a new vice president of business development and agent training for support. We’re doing a lot of exciting things here at the Jonathan Carbutti Real Estate Group. Whether you’re new or an established agent who is struggling with business consistency, I would love to have an honest conversation about what strategies are (and aren’t) working for you and ways that we can help you balance your work and life. Don’t hesitate to reach out to me if you’d like to have this discussion. I’d be glad to lend you my expertise so that your business can thrive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 13:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-is-your-business-flourishing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-is-your-business-flourishing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sitting Down With an Agent: Jim Nardi</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/8rl92CAGzzM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Realtor Jim Nardi sat down with us to tell us about his journey to becoming a real estate professional.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Nardi graduated from Western Connecticut State University where he played football for four years. He likes being in disciplined environments, which came in handy for his career as a Realtor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he decided to work in real estate, Jim was looking for a team environment, which is just what he got here at Carbutti Realtors. He didn’t see other brokerages offer the same kind of support that we do here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the hardest parts of getting involved with the business was getting on the phone to make cold calls.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s not an easy process; he knew it would be hard work, but even still, he underestimated just how hard it would be. In the end, however, the support he received helped him boost his confidence. It took a few months for him to get the hang of it, but his hard work paid off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Jim was looking for a team environment, which is just what he got here at Carbutti Realtors.%20http://localhost:4000/sitting-down-with-an-agent-jim-nardi.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Jim was looking for a team environment, which is just what he got here at Carbutti Realtors.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about what life is like for agents on the Carbutti Realtors Team, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d love to tell you more about how we provide structure and support to all our professionals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 14:53:37 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/sitting-down-with-an-agent-jim-nardi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/sitting-down-with-an-agent-jim-nardi.html</guid>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why New Agents Need to Double Down on the Basics</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_Qp1JUM8I_0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align:center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The market is booming—but don’t get complacent, agents.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, the market is booming, and yes, houses are flying off the shelves. To some of the newer agents to the business, the real estate industry might almost seem easy—all they have to do is put a house on the market and they can sell it in a day. However, today I want to remind all of you that this is not a typical real estate market. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why &lt;strong&gt;now more than ever, it’s important for agents to get a good handle on the basics&lt;/strong&gt; of real estate, including practicing scripts and dialogues, protecting your time, getting into a schedule, and learning the business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=This is not a typical real estate market.%20http://localhost:4000/why-new-agents-need-to-double-down-on-the-basics.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“This is not a typical real estate market.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the market changes from being such a hot seller’s market to more of a buyer’s market where houses sit on the market for a lot longer than they are now, you’ll have to use different strategies to get the homes sold. That’s when your experience and your reference points are truly going to matter. The experienced agents who embrace consistency and protect their time are going to be the ones who thrive when the market changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have brand-new agents who are crushing it right now. One of my agents who was licensed in February already has five sales under his belt. Part of the reason that he’s doing so well is that he has access to great mentoring and coaching; &lt;strong&gt;if you’re new to the industry, you need to find a broker that fits your values&lt;/strong&gt; and is willing to provide the support and coaching you need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to discuss your strategies and business plan or you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 20:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-new-agents-need-to-double-down-on-the-basics.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-new-agents-need-to-double-down-on-the-basics.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: How Can You Create a Real Estate Fanbase?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/K9wrXypKeiA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Be sure to leverage the power of video and social media to your advantage.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You aren’t in the real estate business—you’re in the people business. That’s something that many real estate agents need to be reminded of. As agents, we’re also in the branding and marketing business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2020, the real estate industry is also all about creating a fanbase. We live in the age of social media platforms like Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, and YouTube, which gives you many different avenues to help increase your fanbase. Regardless of the platform, &lt;strong&gt;you need to have a consistent strategy for your branding.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Video is also key, and luckily, videos are simpler than ever to make. We have team members who are finally beginning to dip their toes in the waters of using video as part of their branding and overall strategy, and &lt;strong&gt;they’ve seen amazing results&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love to sit down and have a conversation with you about your business and show you some of our branding strategies that are so easy to implement. Give us a call or send an email, or else we could schedule a video call via Zoom. I hope to hear from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 12:03:55 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-how-can-you-create-a-real-estate-fanbase.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-how-can-you-create-a-real-estate-fanbase.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Q: What’s Our New Normal?</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/9-7ghMSRtac?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’ve made changes to continue helping our clients amid COVID-19.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last few weeks have been difficult because of the global pandemic and what’s going on in the real estate market. We all wait for the spring market every year, and this time it’s been disrupted. Remarkably, despite that, our team just experienced the busiest April we’ve had in three years, and we haven’t missed a beat. We’re doing some things a bit differently right now in regard to how we’re running our business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Our team just experienced the busiest April we’ve had in three years.%20http://localhost:4000/q-whats-our-new-normal.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Our team just experienced the busiest April we’ve had in three years.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our new normal is meeting with clients virtually&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;and having them sign documents via DocuSign.&lt;/strong&gt; Some may see these changes as negatives, but I see the opposite. I love the way the real estate industry is going with this. Honestly, I want things to stay like this even after the health crisis abates; I enjoy doing everything electronically. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have virtual home selling webinars every Thursday evening at 6:30. I can share my screen to show participants what I’m discussing and answer any questions they have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If any of you are considering a career in real estate, it’s not the time to put your plans on hold. This is the time to get into the real estate market because it’s alive and well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to talk about your business with me, call or email anytime. Also, reach out if you have any questions. I would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 13:25:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/q-whats-our-new-normal.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/q-whats-our-new-normal.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>An Example of What Working on a Great Team Gives You</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cS9A9reM58g?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re on a real estate team like ours, you’re part of a well-oiled machine that helps everyone do more business. Here are just a few of the benefits of being on our team.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this edition of our agent training blog, we’re doing something a little bit different. I’m pulling into a house in Oxford on Holley Rd. that we just sold for $15,000 over asking price. &lt;strong&gt;The funny part is that right now is the first time I’m actually seeing the property in person.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a 3,200 square foot house with a separate, private, in-law entry door. I wanted to see the finished product, of course, but I also wanted to talk about the power of having a team around you that can help get homes like this sold for top dollar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This home is professionally staged, as you can see in the video above.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s got a great kitchen, too. Staging shows buyers how a home should be lived in, and good staging shows off all the space available in bedrooms, bathrooms, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=If you’re not offering services like staging and photography, you’re at a competitive disadvantage.%20http://localhost:4000/an-example-of-what-working-on-a-great-team-gives-you.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“If you’re not offering services like staging and photography, you’re at a competitive disadvantage.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although it is possible to be a successful solo agent, most of the successful agents out there work as part of a team. &lt;strong&gt;The power of being on a team means you have more resources, accountability, and power in the marketplace.&lt;/strong&gt; Instead of one person doing everything, each person does one thing at an expert level. For example, this property was leveraged, staged, and sold before I even got a chance to see it in person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not offering services like professional staging, photography, and everything else under the sun, you’re at a competitive disadvantage. It’s all about being relevant in the marketplace so you can get the business, win the listing, add to the buyer experience, and get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in talking about the services our team offers to our agents and how you can do more business on our team, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I’d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 11:59:02 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/an-example-of-what-working-on-a-great-team-gives-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/an-example-of-what-working-on-a-great-team-gives-you.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mindset, Methodology, and Motivation</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nDicRRQbsZU?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listening to practical and motivating podcasts in the morning can make a difference. Here’s how.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been in real estate for 22 years, and recently, I’ve enjoyed getting back to the basics of it all; &lt;strong&gt;I’ve been starting my days by focusing on mindset.&lt;/strong&gt; Motivational podcasts have been a huge part of my intellectual diet, and some really good ones include &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.thebrianbuffinishow.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Brian Buffini’s podcast&lt;/a&gt; and a program titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.listennotes.com/podcasts/real-estate-agent-success-calls-mike-iGZpuElVcfX/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Real Estate Success Calls&lt;/a&gt;. Both have so much to offer newer agents. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Mindset molds how the rest of your day will go.%20http://localhost:4000/mindset-methodology-and-motivation.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Mindset molds how the rest of your day will go.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the latter podcast, real-life agents talk about how they’ve been exactly where you are now in your real estate career and how they were able to take things to the next level—the methodology, the motivations, and every little thing in between. &lt;strong&gt;Just by getting your mind right in the morning by listening to these podcasts before starting your workday, you will see an exponential growth over time.&lt;/strong&gt; Mindset molds how the rest of your day will go. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to have an honest and vulnerable conversation about your real estate business, don’t hesitate to reach out to me by phone or email. I’d love to hear from you and discuss how to make the leap from amateur to pro.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 10:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/mindset-methodology-and-motivation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/mindset-methodology-and-motivation.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Staying in a Routine Is Essential to Real Estate Success</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/rQhRe2EL8YM?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Successful agents are accountable, and they also stick to a routine. Here’s how the top agents on our team do it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to take your career in real estate to the next level, you need to stay in a routine. It’s a simple concept, but as someone who has been in real estate for 22 years, &lt;strong&gt;one common thread among successful agents is accountability. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here at Carbutti &amp;amp; Co., we really put a focus on achieving things together. It’s not just about one agent doing their own thing, although you can have success as an individual agent. However, &lt;strong&gt;there’s a certain power to working on a team in terms of mindshare, resources, and the power of controlling the saleable inventory.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone on our team understands their role. We have an inside sales department, a full-time social media manager, professional photographers, and more. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Everyone on our team has a specific role.%20http://localhost:4000/why-staying-in-a-routine-is-essential-to-real-estate-success.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Everyone on our team has a specific role.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real estate is all about dollar-producing activities and non-dollar-producing activities. I believe &lt;strong&gt;we’ve done a great job of training our agents on those dollar-producing activities and how best to execute them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions for me about what we do, or if you’re interested in bringing your real estate career to the next level, don’t hesitate to reach out by giving me a call or sending an email. I look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 15:52:51 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-staying-in-a-routine-is-essential-to-real-estate-success.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/why-staying-in-a-routine-is-essential-to-real-estate-success.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Importance of Marketing in a Successful Real Estate Business</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/j3xY32TB8g0?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A career in the real estate business is also a career in the marketing business. Here’s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’re almost into 2020, but before we get there, I have a message for you. Everybody wants to get into the real estate business, but if you’re getting into the real estate business right now, you’re actually getting into the marketing business as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, when you’re thinking about a career in real estate, you’re entering one of the most competitive businesses out there. This means that you don’t want to look like everyone else.
You want to stand out from the crowd. The best way to stand out is through your marketing. Whether it’s through radio, TV, advertising, social media, you have got to look different than every other agent and you’ve got to make an impression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=You want to stand out from the crowd in this business.%20http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-marketing-in.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“You want to stand out from the crowd in this business.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here at Carbutti and Co., we’re committed to having a social media manager, along with different marketing strategies and value propositions. If you’re thinking about a career in real estate and you don’t want to go it alone, give us a call or send us an email today. I look forward to hearing from you soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 16:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-marketing-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-importance-of-marketing-in.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
